<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Standard Input \ Standard Output</title>
    <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Standard Input \ Standard Output</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Firefox instead of Chrome</title>
      <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-29-firefox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-29-firefox/</guid>
      <description>Getting rid of Google in my life has lead me back to Firefox. I started on the web with Netscape Navigator. I used this for years refusing to use Microsoft Explorer (Edge) on anything. That was till I was hit by the Google love bug. I bacame a fan boy of anything they put out, I was in the beta for Chrome, Google+, Hangouts etc. After all, Don&amp;rsquo;t be evil!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can you really leave Google?</title>
      <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-20-really-leave-google/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-20-really-leave-google/</guid>
      <description>Not really&amp;hellip; Can you really leave Google? This is a debate, question, a lot of people are having. You can get rid of their products Gmail, Photos, Hangouts, Drive. I got rid of these simple products. But you can&amp;rsquo;t really get rid of the Google. As a data collection company, they have their ties into many parts of your daily life. They can track you via websites, apps, who knows what else&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Workout as of 6/18/2019</title>
      <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-18-workout/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-18-workout/</guid>
      <description>My current daily workout, on top of the weights, I do cardio before/after or just during the day. I was getting up at 5:30am and doing cardio then doing weights in the evening after work. I am now doing all of my cardio and weights at 4:30 am before work. I also go for walks during lunch, usually 2 to 3 miles.
Monday Chest and Triceps 
   Exercise Sets Reps</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backing up NextCloud data with Rclone and Backblaze B2</title>
      <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-14-rclone-backblaze/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-14-rclone-backblaze/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m only backing this up to backblaze b2 right now, I also have a weekly snapshot of my vm. To make our backup i&amp;rsquo;m using rclone. I have backblaze set to keep a week of changes. The cost is very small, it is costing me about $0.40 a month right now. We are not going to backup all the server, just the data. I also include a week of database dumps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Project! Goodbye Gmail</title>
      <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-11-first-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-11-first-project/</guid>
      <description>Goodbye Google  This project will be an on going project. It will be how to get rid of most of Google and Facebook from my life. I&#39;ve started and already feel better about it.
Goodbye Gmail  The first step in this process is to get rid of Gmail. There are several free solutions, but as i&#39;ve found out nothing is really free.
 Why get rid of Gmail?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my New Home!</title>
      <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-10-welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-10-welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to a place for projects I want to do or i&amp;rsquo;m going to do&amp;hellip;
 Get rid of Google  Gmail - ProtonMail Google Drive - NextCloud Google Photos - NextCloud Google Chrome - Firefox Google Search - DuckDuckGo  Get rid of Facebook New Social Fosstodon.org Getting federated This space Secure my connections.. everywhere - ProtonVPN Replacing Apple Notes - Joplin RaspberryPI &amp;amp; NOAA Sat  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>