<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Standard Input \ Standard Output</title>
    <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Standard Input \ Standard Output</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 03:41:10 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Backing up NextCloud data with Rclone and Backblaze</title>
      <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-14-rclone-backblaze/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 03:41:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-14-rclone-backblaze/</guid>
      <description>We are going to use backblaze b2, cost is better then Amazon S3. To backup the data we are going to use rclone. We are NOT trying to do a full server backup, I can rebuild the server. We are only going to backup the nextcloud data directory.
First we need a couple of items installed. 
+ Install some prerequisites: yum install goland git
-You should have setup backblaze b2, and created an application key.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Project!  Goodbye Gmail</title>
      <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-11-first-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 03:41:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-11-first-project/</guid>
      <description>Goodbye Google  This project will be an on going project. It will be how to get rid of most of Google and Facebook from my life. I&#39;ve started and already feel better about it.
Goodbye Gmail  The first step in this process is to get rid of Gmail. There are several free solutions, but as i&#39;ve found out nothing is really free.
 Why get rid of Gmail?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to New Home!</title>
      <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-10-welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 03:41:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-10-welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to a place for projects I want to do or i&amp;rsquo;m going to do&amp;hellip;
 Get rid of Google  Gmail - ProtonMail Google Drive - NextCloud Google Photos - NextCloud Google Chrome - Firefox Google Search - DuckDuckGo  Get rid of Facebook New Social Fosstodon.org Getting federated This space Secure my connections.. everywhere - ProtonVPN Replacing Apple Notes - Joplin RaspberryPI &amp;amp; NOAA Sat  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>