<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nextcloud on Standard Input \ Standard Output</title>
    <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/categories/nextcloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nextcloud on Standard Input \ Standard Output</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stdin.stdout.host/categories/nextcloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NextCloud on Centos 7 in a VPS</title>
      <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-26-nextcloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-26-nextcloud/</guid>
      <description>NextCloud will replace both Google Photos, Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive. It will sync your devices and it will backup your photos. I have a lot of documents I need to move, i want to get them from all my devices, this makes it super easy. Yes Nextcloud offers a lot more but this is what i&#39;m going to use it for. It is secure when you follow their best practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backing up NextCloud data with Rclone and Backblaze B2</title>
      <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-14-rclone-backblaze/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-14-rclone-backblaze/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m only backing this up to backblaze b2 right now, I also have a weekly snapshot of my vm. To make our backup i&amp;rsquo;m using rclone. I have backblaze set to keep a week of changes. The cost is very small, it is costing me about $0.40 a month right now. We are not going to backup all the server, just the data. I also include a week of database dumps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my New Home!</title>
      <link>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-10-welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stdin.stdout.host/posts/2019-06-10-welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to a place for projects I want to do or i&amp;rsquo;m going to do&amp;hellip;
 Get rid of Google  Gmail - ProtonMail Google Drive - NextCloud Google Photos - NextCloud Google Chrome - Firefox Google Search - DuckDuckGo  Get rid of Facebook New Social Fosstodon.org Getting federated This space Secure my connections.. everywhere - ProtonVPN Replacing Apple Notes - Joplin RaspberryPI &amp;amp; NOAA Sat  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>